Contact

Dublin, Ireland 0870540026 (Mobile) lukaszkukla@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/lukaszkukla (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Purchasing
Logistics
Logistics Management

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)
Polish (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Google Calendar Essential Training Certified Scrum Product Owner (CSPO)

C# Essential Training: 1 Syntax and Object Oriented Programming

Programming Foundations: Algorithms

Lean Six Sigma Green Belt (ICGB)

Lukasz Kukla

IT & Digital Transformation Manager | Project Manager | Full Stack Developer | HTML5, CSS3, Python, SQL, Bootstrap Ireland

Summary

IT & Digital Transformation Program Manager with 14 years of experience, skilled in Operations, IT Service Management, Procurement and Supply Chain. Key strengths include: complex problem solving, practical application of Lean Six Sigma methodology, excellent communication and relationship management. I am highly resourceful, reliable and well organized. Skilled to work in a fast-paced environment across multiple competing priorities and projects.

Experience

Exertis Ireland
Stock Control and Vendor Manager
September 2021 - Present (9 months)
Dublin, County Dublin, Ireland

Projekt Wentylacja Co-Founder June 2020 - Present (2 years)

Confidential

IT & Digital Transformation Manager July 2018 - June 2020 (2 years) County Dublin, Ireland

- Program manager for creating and launching eCommerce website and mobile application (iOS, Android) for B2B customers (expected adoption: 2500 B2B users)
- Digitized and automated quotation, custom stock ordering and tracking system
- Created and implemented IT infrastructure company security standards
- Monitoring service levels, incidents, process and change management across key IT infrastructure inc. networks, hardware, anti-virus, security protection and phone service

• Full IT budget forecasting and management

Lennox Laboratory Supplies Ltd Procurement Executive March 2018 - August 2018 (6 months)

Dublin, Leinster, Ireland

- Lead Program Manager for implementation new procurement processes
- Evaluate current state of the supply chain and identify risks
- Negotiate and manage supplier contracts and SLAs and carry out supplier appraisals
- Support Sales with the submission of Customer Tenders
- Identify new partners strategic suppliers and build relationships including Joint Ventures
- Optimise and rationalise existing supplier and product portfolio

Sign & Digital Materials Ltd.

12 years 8 months

Procurement and Supply Chain Manager April 2008 - March 2018 (10 years)

Dublin, Ireland

- Key IT Project Manager, Lead Warehouse stock manager across 2 locations and team of 7 employees
- Automation of functions within purchasing and procurement department
- · Introduced barcoding capabilities to warehouse processes
- Led introduction of inventory analysis and management system
- · Managed opening of new warehouse in Northern Ireland, full launch
- Implemented company's procurement strategy and managed 120+ full supplier relations with 5000+ active SKUs
- Responsible for IT contractual service level management, risk assessment, incident management and change management across 4 IT companies (in ERP, CRM, Phone and IT infrastructure with software)
- Program Manager for Sign+Digital's website and e-commerce platform for online shopping
- Lead number of marketing projects, including production of Creative Guide company's product catalogue with 343 pages and over 4500 SKUs
- Deployment of five Creative Cruisers (mobile shops) across Ireland,
 Northern Ireland and the UK fully stocked mobile shops which serve our sales team as USP when visiting customers

Procurement and Supply Chain Assistant August 2006 - March 2008 (1 year 8 months)

Management of inventory across multiple warehouses. Delivery of optimum mix of products "just-in-time"

Maintenance of purchasing information, files and records in conformance with company's policy and procedures.

Responsible for supplier invoice queries, product issues and resolve claims in compliance with company's policy.

Report and recommend on redundant and obsolete products.

Review and management of customer returns, including product inspection and return validation.

Warehouse Operative August 2005 - July 2006 (1 year) Dublin, Ireland

Education

Code Institute

Diploma i Software Development, Full Stack Software Development · (November 2021 - November 2022)

Dublin Business School

Higher Diploma, Science in Computing - Web and Cloud Technologies · (2019 - 2021)

Dublin Business School

BA (Hons) in Business (Management), Business Administration, Management and Operations \cdot (2012 - 2015)

Irish Institute of Purchasing and Materials Management (IIPMM)
Bachelor of Business Ordinary Degree in Procurement and Supply
Management, Purchasing, Procurement/Acquisitions and Contracts
Management · (2009 - 2012)